Guide to the North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
- Photographs, 1969-2010; 1969 2010
  - Photo CDs and DVDs, 2002-2010; 2002 2010
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 3, G-H (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 4, I-L (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 5, M-O (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 6, P-R (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 7, S-Tr (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 8, Tu-Z (Cdbox 12)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 1, 21st Birthday-Art to Wear (Cdbox 39)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 2, Art to Wear - Design Camp (Cdbox 39)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 3, Design Camp - Egyptian Protest (Cdbox 39)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 4, Egyptian Protest - GLBT (Cdbox 39)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 5, GLBT - Krispy Kreme Challenge (Cdbox 46)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 6, Krispy Kreme Challenge - Men's Basketball (Cdbox 46)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 7, Men's Basketball - Snow Day (Cdbox 46)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 8, Snow Day - Student Media (Cdbox 46)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 9, Student Media - Women's Tennis (Cdbox 46)
    - 2010-2011 Photo Archive - Disk 10, Women's Tennis - Zumba (Cdbox 46)
    - Theresa, 22 February 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - A Cappella Group, 26 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - ACC Men's Tennis - Andrew Knopp, 25 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - "Ag Stuff" Edited 1/21/03 [Athletics, Fair, Students], 21 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - "Ag Stuff 2" Edited 1/21/03 au Football, 21 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Anti-War Rally 1/2 - Ritter, 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Anti-War Rally 2/2, 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Big Event - Lindsay McDonald, 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Black Fitness - Tynesha, 10 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Brent Road 1/2 - Carl Hudson, 23 September 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Brickyard Campaign for SBP, 14 April 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Business Management [Winter campus shots] - Timny, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Campus Activities] - Theresa, 25 February 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Chorus], 7 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Construction - Annamarie Cade, 30 September 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Cross Country - Rob Bradley, 30 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Cross Country (2) - Rob Bradley, 30 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Delta Upsilon, 7 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Department of Business -Timmy, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Edited Photos 1/5/03 (1) [Student Life], January 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Edited Photos 1/5/03 (2) [Football, Greek Life, Soccer], January 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Feature - Annamarie Cade, 5 October 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Feature - Carl Hudson, 23 September 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Feature - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Feature - Carl Hudson, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Football] (1 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (2 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (3 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (4 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (5 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (6 of 6), 16 January 2004 (Cdbox 12)
    - [Football] (1 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Football] (2 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Football] (3 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Football] (4 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Football] (5 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Football] (6 of 6), 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - Football vs. Duke +cromes 1/2 - Josh Michel, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. Duke 2/2 - Josh Michel, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. Duke 1/4 +crome - W. Boyle, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. Duke 2/4 - W. Boyle, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. Duke 3/4 - W. Boyle, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Football] vs. Duke 4/4 - W. Boyle, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs. Duke, Crowd, and Band], 19 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. East Tennessee State University 1/5 - Rob Bradley, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. East Tennessee State University 2/5 - Rob Bradley, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. East Tennessee State University 3/5 - Rob Bradley, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. East Tennessee State University 4/5 - Rob Bradley, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. East Tennessee State University 5/5 - Rob Bradley, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Florida State University 1/5 - Rich Lawrence, 10 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs. Florida State University] - Rich Lawrence, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Florida State University 2/5 - Rich Lawrence, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Florida State University 3/5 - Rich Lawrence, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs. Florida State University] 4/5 - Rich Lawrence, 10 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. Florida State University 6 - Rich Lawrence, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs. Maryland and Bell Tower] - Erica Tuers, 1 February 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. New Mexico 1/5 - Andrew Knopp, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. New Mexico 2/5 - Andrew Knopp, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. New Mexico 3/5 - Andrew Knopp, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. New Mexico 4/5 - Andrew Knopp, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. New Mexico 5/5 - Andrew Knopp, 24 September 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. New Mexico - Kyle Rodgers, 24 August 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. Texas Tech - Kuz, 15 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Football vs. Texas Tech (2) - Kuz, 15 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Texas Tech (3) - Kuz, 15 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Texas Tech (4) - Kuz, 15 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] Texas Tech (5) - Kuz, 15 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] University of Massachusetts - Josh Aycock, 7 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] University of Massachusetts 2 - Josh Aycock, 7 October 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] University of Massachusetts 3 - Josh Aycock, 7 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Football vs.] University of Massachusetts 4 -Josh Aycock, 7 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Football vs. Universiy of Virginia- UVA 6 NCSU 9 - Mike Pittman, 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Fox [Hall?] - Rob Bradley, 21 January 2005 (Cdbox 12)
    - Graduation - Carl Hudson, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Headshots] Taylor Color CD 1, 2002-2003 (Cdbox 39)
    - Hindu Worship - Carl Hudson, 3 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Homecoming Parade 1/2 - Carl Hudson, 26 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Homecoming Parade 2/2 - Carl Hudson, 26 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Honk for Peace - David, 11 April 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Ice Storm - Boyle, Gator Bowl [press conference] - Tim, 21 January 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - International Night - Dora, 22 February 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - International Fashion Show - Carl Hudson, 1 March 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Javanese Gamelon - Rob Bradley, 17 April 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Jennie Smith, 25 September 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Krimson and Krean - Brad Callare, 10 March 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Landmarks - Tynesha, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Law Fair - Carl Hudson, 26 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Legends - Tynesha, 9 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Meeting about the Chancellor - Boyle, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Boston College - Josh Michel, 16 January 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Men's] Basketball vs. Boston College - Josh Michel, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Men's] Basketball vs. Boston College - Michael, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Men's] Basketball [vs. Clemson], 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Duke], 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Duke], 10 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Florida State, Duke], 10 March 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Georgia Tech 1], 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Georgia Tech 2], 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Men's Basketball vs. Georgia Tech] - Worthum?, 6 March 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Men's Basketball vs. University of Virginia - Boyle, 19 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Men's Basketball vs. University of Virgina (2) - Boyle, 19 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Men's Basketball vs. University of Virginia - Boyle, 21 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Radford 1/2 - Rob Bradley, 9 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Radford 2/2 - Rob Bradley, 9 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Minority Fair - Carl Hudson, 3 October 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Monster's Ball - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Music Festival - Carl Hudson, 23 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Music Festival 2/2 - Carl Hudson, 23 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Mystery Roll [Art] - Carl Hudson, 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Mystery Roll [Men's Basketball vs. Duke], 30 September 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - NC State Student Pose Change, 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Nuke Plant - Lane, 10 March 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Orchestra - Matt, 22 February 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Recreate State - Erica Tuers, 6 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Samuel Tso, Code Talker - Carl Hudson, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - [Skateboarding and Concerts], 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Snow], 6 February 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - Sorority S.P. - Rian Thomas, 25 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - State Fair 1/5 - Carl Hudson, 5 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - State Fair 2/5 - Carl Hudson, 5 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - State Fair 3/5 - Carl Hudson, 5 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - State Fair 4/5 - Carl Hudson, 5 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - State Fair 5/5 - Carl Hudson, 5 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Student Life- Merry Wives of Windsor 1/1 - Carl Hudson, 26 November 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Student Life Step Show - Annamarie Cade, 12 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Student Life- Up All Night - Carl Hudson, 26 November 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Student Life- Wear Red and Get Fed -Tim Lytvimento, 11 November 2002 (Cdbox 3)
    - Student Life Winter Concert - Tynesha, 10 January 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - [Student studying], 19 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Students at night], 9 December 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - [Students eating], 6 February 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Students on brickyard], 19 February 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - [Students on brickyard and in cafeteria], 19 February 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - Students Day at the Capitol, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Swimming vs. Duke 1/2 - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Swimming vs. Duke 2/2 - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Tailgating 1/4 - Lindsay McDonald, 9 December 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Team Photos - Grant Halverson, 2002-2003 (Cdbox 3)
    - Technician Office?, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Textile College - Dave, 1 March 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Textile College - Kuz, 13 March 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - TTSA Group Shots - Boyle, 11 February 2003 (Cdbox 2)
    - Volleyball vs. University of North Carolina 1/2 - Carl Hudson, 30 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Volleyball vs. University of North Carolina 2/2 - Carl Hudson, 30 October 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Weekend Excursion, Greek Life - Andrew Knopp, 20 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Wolves - Andrew Knopp, 26 September 2006 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Women's] Basketball vs. Boston College [Clemson], 10 February 2003 (Cdbox 1)
    - [Women's Basketball vs. Virginia], 27 January 2004 (Cdbox 39)
    - Women's Board - Take Back the Night, 14 January 2002 (Cdbox 1)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Florida State University 1/3 - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Florida State University 2/3 - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Florida State University 3/3 - Carl Hudson, 28 October 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Women's Tennis, ACC - Andrew Knopp, 25 September 2002 (Cdbox 2)
    - Damaged CDs and DVDs, 1998-2005 (Cdbox 47)
  - Photographic Prints, 1969-1998; 1969 1998
    - Accessible Gardening, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Aerobics, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - African American Heritage Festival, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Ag Week, 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Quilt and Memorial Service, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Airplanes, 1986, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Alcohol, 1984-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Alumni, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Amber Photomicrograph, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Angelou, Maya, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Animal Resources Staff, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Animals, 1984-1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Anthony, Susan B. Dinner, 17 February 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Anti-hate Rally, 3 March 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Arabian Night Performance, 18 March 1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Arboretum at NCSU, 12 January 1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Arcade on Hillsborough Street, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Archery, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Arlington Bridge, 1969? (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Army, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Arts and Crafts, 1989-1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Artsplosure, 22 May 1994 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - AT and T Sweepstakes, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Awards, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Azalea Festival, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Bagel Shop on Hillsborough Street, 5 October 1994 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Bagpipes, Symphony, NC State Pep Band, 1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Barbers, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Barlaz, Dr. Morton A., undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Bars, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Baseball, 1992-1997, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Batchelor, Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Beach, 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bear Studies, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Benson Mule Days, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Bicycles, 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Black History Speakers, Marches, 1989-1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Blanc, Mel, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Blood Drive, 1988-1996 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Boating, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Bomb Threat, 24 January 1987 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Books, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Bookstores, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Bowling, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Brent Road, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - The Brewery, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Brickyard Preacher, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Buildings in Raleigh, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Buses - Wolfline, Nightlife Shuttle, 1983, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Bush, George H.W., 1990, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Businesses, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Campaigns (political), 1982-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Camping, 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Camping - Joyce Kilmer (includes negatives), undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Campus Buildings (1 of 2), 1982-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Campus Buildings (2 of 2), 1981-1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Campus Renovations, 1981-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Canned Food Drive, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Cantina, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Car Accidents, 1987-1994, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Car show, Car Smash, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Carcass Found in Sullivan Lounge, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Cartoons, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Career Placement Center and Career Fair, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Carlton, Charles, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Carowinds Theme Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Casino Night, 17 February 1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Caterpillar Footwear Marketing Materials (includes slides), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - CBS College Tour, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Cemeteries, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Central Campus Craze, 1982, 1987, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Campus, 1987-1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Chancellor's Liason Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Change Day, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Charity Fundraisers, 1987, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - CHASSnet Career Networking Fair, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Chemical Spill, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Children, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Chimney Rock (includes negatives), undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Chinese New Year, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Chinese Night, 1979, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Chorus, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Christmas, 1983, 1990, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Civil Engineering, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Classes, 1983-1996 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "Click It or Ticket" Promotional Materials, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Climbing Wall, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Clinton, Bill, 1993, undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Cloggers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Clowns, 1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Clubs at NCSU, 1994, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - College Bowl, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - College Republicans, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Comic Books, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Compassionate Living Fair, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Computers, 1984-1998 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Concessions, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Construction, 1981-1994 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Counseling Center, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Court of North Carolina, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Craft Center, 1983-1993 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Credit Card Promotions on Campus, undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Cricket, undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Crisp, James, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Cuculo, John, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Dancers, 1985-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Daniels, Josephus (Birthplace Marker), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Robert F., undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Daytona Beach, Florida, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Dead for a Day, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Deans of Schools, 1977, 1986, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Demonstrations, 1973?, 1984, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Design Camp, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Design School, 1988-1994, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Dinosaurs (professor teaching about them), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Dog Day Race, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Dorm Rooms, 1988-1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Dortch, Stacy, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Draft Registration, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Drains, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Driving, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Drugs, 1987, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Dukakis, Mike and Kitty, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Duraleigh Connector Site, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Durham Bulls, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Dyeing Machinge at College of Textiles, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Earth Day, 1990, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Ebert, Roger, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Eclipse, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Edwards, Reese, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Elders, Jocelyn, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Electric Company Mall, 1986, 1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Electronics, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Emergency Responders, 1983, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Emerging Issues Forum, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Employee Appreciation, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Energy Usage, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Equestrian Club, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Faculty and Staff Appreciation Day, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Faircloth, Lauch, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Farmer's Market, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Fashion, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Financial Aid, 1980, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Fires, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Fireworks, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Fishing, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Flea Market, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Flooding, 1985, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Fog, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Food, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Football, 1980-1996, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Forests, 1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Fountain, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - France, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Fraternity and Sorority Activities, 1983-1994 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Free Expression Tunnel, 1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Frisbee Team, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Frost Bite Trip (includes negatives), undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Ft. Loudon Dam in 1942, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Galifianicas, Mark, undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Gant, Harvey (rally), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Gay and Lesbian Blue Jeans Day, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Generator by Bragaw, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Glee Club, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Golden Gate Bridge, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Golf, undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Goodall, Jane, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Graduation, 1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Grains of Time (A Cappella Group), undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Green, Vanalyne, undated (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Grenada Invasion (maps), undated (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Grenadeer Guards, undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Griffin, Clifford, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Guest Speakers, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Gymnastics, 1996-1997, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Haley, Alex, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Halloween, 1983-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Hands Across Campus, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hawk, Jack, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Headline News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Health, 1981-1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Hinn, Benny, 1997? (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Hockey, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Homecoming, 1984, 1991, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Homicides, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Hope, Bob, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Huffman, Van, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Hunt, Jim, 1984-1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Hurricane Andrew, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Hurricane Diana, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hutchins, Martha, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The Icehouse, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Improv, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Incubation, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Independence Day, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Indian Night, 1990, 1995, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - International Coffee Hour, 1985, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - International Dance Troupe, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - International Fair, 1972-1991, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - International Students, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Ives, Burl, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Jackson, Jesse, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Jade Garden Restaurant, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jeep Eagle Health and Fitness Tour, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Jett, J.B., undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Jones, Robert "Roddy", undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Kachuk, Lori T., 1992? (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Kauffman, Terry, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Kellison, Robert, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - King, Yolanda, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Kings Dominion Amusement Park, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Kitty in Flight store on Hillsborough Street, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Knife Incident, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Laser, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Laundry, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Lawn Party, 1993-1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Leaders of the Pack, 1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Lectures, 1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Lee, Donna, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Library, 1973-1995 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Lighthouse Cove (Corolla Light, NC), 1994 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Magician Bob Kramer, undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Maintenance, 1993, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)